question_data=[
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "True"
      ]
   },
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"The television show Doctor Who first aired in 1963.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "False"
      ]
   },
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"In the TV series Red Dwarf, Kryten&#039;s full name is Kryten 2X4B-523P.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "False"
      ]
   },
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"Like his character in &quot;Parks and Recreation&quot;, Aziz Ansari was born in South Carolina.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "False"
      ]
   },
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"Bob Ross was a US Air Force pilot.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "True"
      ]
   },
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "True"
      ]
   },
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons respect William Shakespeare, they even suspect him having a Klingon lineage.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "False"
      ]
   },
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are commonly referred to as &quot;Black Elves&quot;.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "True"
      ]
   },
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"In &quot;Star Trek: The Next Generation&quot;, Data is the only android in existence.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "True"
      ]
   },
   {
      "category":"Entertainment: Television",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"An episode of &quot;The Simpsons&quot; is dedicated to Moe Szyslak&#039;s bar rag.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
         "False"
      ]
   }
]